billionairesaustralia.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy - Billionaires Newswire

This following document sets forth the Privacy Policy for the Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd website, [www.billionairesnewswire.com](http://www.billionairesnewswire.com/).

Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd is committed to providing you with the best possible customer service experience. Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Crh), which sets out a number of principles concerning the privacy of individuals.

## Collection of your personal information

There are many aspects of the site which can be viewed without providing personal information, however, for access to future Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd customer support features you are required to submit personally identifiable information. This may include but not limited to a unique username and password, or provide sensitive information in the recovery of your lost password.

## Sharing of your personal information

We may occasionally hire other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not limited to handling customer support enquiries, processing transactions or customer freight shipping. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

## Use of your personal information

For each visitor to reach the site, we expressively collect the following non-personally identifiable information, including but not limited to browser type, version and language, operating system, pages viewed while browsing the Site, page access times and referring website address. This collected information is used solely internally for the purpose of gauging visitor traffic, trends and delivering personalized content to you while you are at this Site.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd reserves the right to make amendments to this Privacy Policy and will notify members on any changes of data use. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site.

## Accessing Your Personal Information

You have a right to access your personal information, subject to exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to do so, please let us know. You may be required to put your request in writing for security reasons.

## Contacting us

Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and would like further information, please contact us by any of the following means during business hours Monday to Friday.

Post: Attn: Privacy Policy,  
Billionaires Newswire Pty Ltd,  
Suite 99, 26-32 Pirrama Road,  
Pyrmont, 2009,  
AUSTRALIA

E-mail: [info@billionairesaustralia.com](mailto:info@billionairesaustralia.com)
